https://www.windsorplywood.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
General
This Privacy Policy applies to the privacy of users of the www.windsorplywood.com web site (hereinafter “ Site” ). This privacy policy outlines the information that Windsor Plywood and their franchisees, distributors and affiliates (collectively the “ Company,” “ we” or “ us” ), will collect during your visit to the Site and how we will use the information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other activities of the Company.
Internet Privacy and Information Collected
We respect your right to privacy. We do not collect personally identifiable information (for example your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) about you from the Site unless you voluntarily provide it to us. During your visit to the Site, we will collect non-personally identifiable information regarding your usage of the Site. We use this information to monitor Site usage, enhance the Site and as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy or on the Site. You may visit the Site without providing any personally identifiable information.
Personal Information
We will only collect personal information, which will be limited to your name, e-mail and address if you choose to enter that information.
Information Shared with Third Parties
Unless otherwise stated at the time of collection, we do not sell or disclose personally identifiable information provided to us to any third parties (other than business partners of the Company and third party vendors retained by the Company). There are exceptions to this policy, such as: (a) you specifically authorize the disclosure or (b) disclosure is necessary to provide service to you or (c) disclosure is required by law or (d) disclosure is required for the safety of others. We may also use this information to protect our customers, employees or property – for instance, to investigate fraud, harassment or other types of unlawful service activities involving the Company or other companies that we do business with. Please be aware that when you provide personally identifiable information to us in connection with a transaction or event that we sponsor with a third party, you may also be providing that information to the third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of the third party. We may share non-personally identifiable information with business partners and other third parties to evaluate or enhance the Site. Such information may include, for example, the number of visitors to the Site and the specific pages visited. Non-personally identifiable information may also be disclosed if it is required by law or for the safety of others.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our Site includes links to or frames of Web sites of third parties. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices employed by third party Web sites. Other Web sites may have different privacy policies or no privacy policy. Users should review the privacy policies of any Web site before providing personal information. You should note that we may host Web site advertising that is linked to the Site. If you provide any personally identifiable information while visiting any Web site advertising that is hosted by us, you will also be providing the personally identifiable information to the advertiser. If you provide any personally identifiable information while visiting any third party Web site that is linked from or framed by the Site, you will be providing the personally identifiable information to the third party owner of that site. Please note that we may share non-personally identifiable information collected from any Web site advertising we host on behalf of an advertiser with third parties in order to complete a transaction that you initiated, provide you services or evaluate the hosted Web site.
Opting Out Questions About the Policy
If you do not want us to contact you via e-mail, you can remove your name from our e-mail solicitation lists by contacting webmaster@windsorplywood.com. All concerns or questions about your privacy related to online advertising should be addressed through our Privacy Policy administration, which can also be reached by contacting webmaster@windsorplywood.com.
Communications with Users of the Site
We may contact you and our customers by telephone, direct mail or e-mail to conduct online surveys, provide information on new products and services, or inform you of special promotions. If you receive an e-mail from us that you do not wish to receive, you may contact webmaster@windsorplywood.com and ask us to remove you from our list. Please note that if you do remove yourself from our e-mail list, some e-mail messages may still come to you, although not those dealing with commercial solicitations. For example, we may e-mail you about viruses, or changes to your service, or other types of product advisories.
Cookies
We may use “ cookies” to collect IP addresses and information regarding your usage of the Site. A cookie is a small file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer that is available for future access when you return to the Site. We use cookies to monitor your online activity and provide better service to you.
Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, please note that some Web sites may be able to track your usage after cookie deletion if you come back to the same site or a related site and provide personal information.
Security
We are committed to protecting the security of our user’ s personal information, including when it is transmitted online. We have information systems that collect and store customer information, in addition to systems that store our own business records. These systems have different types of security as appropriate for the information stored. Our databases and systems are maintained to reasonably secure the Company’ s commercial information, including information about its customers.
Children
We recognize the importance of the safety and privacy of children on the Internet. Due to these issues and in order to comply with certain laws, we do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Privacy Policy Updates
We may amend this privacy policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes to this policy, we will make an announcement on the Site.
This policy was last modified on April 14, 2016
Copyright © 2020. Windsor Plywood. All rights reserved.
Sitemap
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
